Hello, Alia.
Hello, James.
How are you?
I am well. Thank you.
I'm good. Thanks.
Where are you from?
I am from the United States of America.
I'm from the United Kingdom.
And how old are you?
I am 30 years old.
How old are you?
I'm 32 years old.
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yes. I have two little sisters.
How about you?
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yes. I have one brother and two sisters.
Alia, what's your favorite food?
My favorite food is a cheeseburger.
How about you? What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is pizza.
And what's your favorite sport?
My favorite sport is snowboarding.
What about you? What's your favorite sport?
My favorite sport is tennis.
Alia, can you swim?
Yes. I can swim.
Can you swim?
And can you ride a bicycle?
Yes. I can ride a bicycle.
Can you ride a bicycle?
Can you drive?
Yes. I can drive.
How about you? Can you drive, James?
Thank you for talking with me today.
Thank you for talking with me.
Bye.