Okay, today we are going to learn about
Running
You can run upstairs run on grass anything
Walking
This is crumpling
Crumpling paper and this is throwing
Catching
Throwing the garbage in the trash throwing and this is jogging it's a little bit different than running or walking
jogging it's in between running walking jogging
That is jogging walking jogging running
That's the difference between those three running jogging walking jump
Oh
And this is to open open open and this is to close close close
Remember if you open something you usually have to close it so they usually go together open and close
This is to sit to sit
I am sitting
Sit this standing I'm standing stand I'm sitting and this is to break
break
Break this is to point I am pointing point you see I'm pointing at the peacocks you see point
Look at that pointing I'm pointing pointing outside pointing at the glass cups now this is
smile
To smile this is frown frown and there's also a very popular saying
Turn that frown upside down. So turn that frown into smile frown
Another emotion is laughing an action laughing haha haha like laughing like
That's funny laughing haha
I thought I just laughed
randomly but that's laughing
This is to sing
Oh
Now I am drawing
I'm drawing
I am not good at drawing I'm not good but I could try I could still try to drop
Okay, so this is hiding I am hiding behind
A curtain and this is hiding also I'm hiding
Hat behind my back now I'm pushing it
pushing it closed
Push
Closed I am pushing it closed push
Pull open pull open pull
This is cleaning I am cleaning the window
cleaning
The window I am writing
I wrote this now crying cry
I am crying
Now listening
I am listening to music I'm listening to music
Okay, so this is sleeping you could sleep on a bed or if you're tired
On your couch
On your sofa or couch
And you would also sleep on a hammock
Going to sleep
And this is waking up waking up
Oh
Waking up I am waking up now now let's learn to wash to wash so you could wash
Laundry dirty laundry you could wash it
I
Am washing my laundry or you could also wash dishes
Wash dishes you see the dishes are dirty so you could wash them
I'm washing a cup
Wash I've just washed the cup after you wash a cup you could put it here for it to dry
Dry now I am reading forbs I'm reading
I could also read on my phone I could read comics manga on my phone I'm reading them to kick
kick
I'm going to kick the sofa kick kick you normally
kick a
soccer ball
But I don't have one kick
That hurt this is a rock
Okay now let's stretch
See what it is
Stretching the next word is scratch I'm scratching my head
I'm scratching my arm scratch
Okay, the next word is to look
I am looking at the horizon to look okay
Look I'm looking I'm looking
This is looking looking under the bed
The next word is yawning
Yawning when you're tired tired
Next is also clapping
clapping
clapping my hands clapping
You clap your hands after a performance movie a speech you clap
clapping means good job you did well clapping can also be sarcastic like
Wow
Good job
sarcastic where you don't really mean it
Another word is texting
Texting when you text someone
Hi, how are you today? I was thinking maybe we'll go Swiss
calling
Hi, yeah, they should subscribe
Like and tell me what country they're from
is
Lying down
Lying down it's not sleeping but just lying down
Now this is to show
Follow my personal Instagram if you want
So I am showing you my
Instagram
So if you want you could follow now I'm watching
TV
I'm watching the television
The TV I'm watching
Hi, what are you doing? Cooking
Cooking
Cooking food
Pork beef cooking in general so right now he's coding
coding the pork
This is the coated pork
This is frying
You'd say all this is cooking is all cooking
Okay, the food has been cooked
So it's done
analysis eat
Okay, so we have the food
Eat
Do you eat you drink
juice or water
I'm drinking
drinking
Okay, the next verb is to talk
This is like talking to someone
Talking to something you can talk to your dog
Your cat a person your coworker
Or you can talk to teddy bear
Hello, how are you? I'm doing good a little bit tired, but I'm okay
What do you think of the weather today? Is it nice?
Is it sunny? Is it cloudy?
Is it misty?
Is it overcast? Do they have the weather is very sunny?
And what is one of your favorite hobbies to do?
What do you like doing on your free time?
Or literally the only sleep
You hear that? That's him
Anyways, this is talking
This is also called conversation
Or talking
He's talking
I'm talking and that's a conversation
And also what I do every day to the camera
When I talk to you guys is talking to
I'm talking
Talk
Now let's talk about buying and selling
Buy and sell
Here you can see I'm on vans
And here you could buy shoes
So you could choose your size
Add it to cart
And then buy them
The store vans is selling shoes
And I am buying shoes
With money
So I'm paying money to buy shoes
So remember I'm buying
So I give money
And they are selling
So they take my money
Receive my money
Usually it's a company that sells
And a person that buys
Okay, this is also driving
You can see it's
Early and I'm driving
This is too fixed
Too fixed as vehicle
In this video
Or to fix a car
To fix anything like this
But usually it's with vehicles
Or repairing something
To fix
If you guys want to see many vlogs
Of confidential input
Make sure to follow my
English Instagram
And if you want to just see me
My personal life
Make sure to follow my personal Instagram
If you want
And again this is where you guys were from
The top five countries
From the last video
If you want to see the top five countries
For this video
Make sure to leave a comment
Where you're from this video
And I'll tell you that in the next video
Finally I have some questions for you guys
The first is what type of videos do you guys want more
You guys want more shorter videos
Like eight to 12 minutes
But more often
Like every two to three days
Or do you want longer videos
Like above 30
Around 30 minutes
To an hour videos
But only once a week
What do you guys prefer
And also do you guys want more
Traveling videos
Of me traveling places
Or just daily life
And also what level of English are you
So I can make videos
For the big majority
Are you guys beginners
Advanced or intermediate
So I can start making more videos for you guys
Again guys thank you for watching
Make sure to like, comment, subscribe
I'll see you guys in the next video
Bye