Hello everybody my name is Sam and welcome back to my A1 series. This is the UK.
This is London in the summer. This is London in the summer. This is a bus. This is London in the summer.
In the summer it is sunny. In the summer it is sunny. Look at this. It is sunny. In the summer it is sunny.
In the summer it is hot. In the summer it is hot. In the summer it is dry. It is dry. It's not wet. It is dry.
In the summer it is dry. In the summer the day is long. The day the day is long. In the summer the day is long.
This is the UK in the winter. This is London in the winter. This is London. This is also London. This is London in the winter.
In the winter it is snow. In the winter it is snow. This is snow. This is snow. This is snow. This is also snow.
Here there is more snow. In the winter it is snow. In the winter it is cold. In the winter it is cold.
In the winter it is very cold.
In the winter it is wet.
In the winter it is wet and it rains.
This is rain.
But in the winter it is wet.
It is not dry.
It is not dry in the winter.
In the winter it is wet.
In the winter the nights are long.
The nights are long.
In the winter the days are short but the nights are long.
In the summer the days are long and the nights are short.
In the winter it is wet.
In the summer it is dry.
In the winter it is cold.
In the winter it is cold and the summer it is hot.
In the summer it is hot.
In the winter it snows.
In the summer it is sunny and the summer it is sunny.
This is the UK in the winter and this is the UK in the summer.
Thank you for watching today's episode and I will see you in part 5.
Bye.