Hi, I'm Justine and I'm back with James for another video in our series.
Today we are talking about sports.
We are talking about sports that we like and sports that we don't like.
James, do you like swimming?
Yes, I do like swimming.
What do I like about swimming?
Well, it's very healthy and it's very good exercise.
And I like swimming, yes, but I really like swimming underwater.
I love swimming underwater.
Justine, do you like swimming?
I only like swimming when it's really hot outside.
I am a very cold person.
I feel cold very easily.
So I don't like swimming in indoor pools.
I only like swimming in outdoor pools, in pools that are outside, only on a very hot day.
So if it is 30 degrees Celsius outside, then I am happy.
I will go swimming.
But I don't like swimming if it's too cold for me.
So I don't like swimming when it's 15 degrees Celsius or 20 degrees Celsius.
That is too cold.
But when it's hot outside, when it's 30 degrees Celsius, then I am happy.
James, do you like tennis?
Yes, I do like tennis.
And I like to hit the ball.
I like to hit the ball with my tennis racket.
Yes, I love to hit the ball with my tennis racket.
Justine, do you like tennis?
Yes, I do like tennis.
I'm not very good at tennis, but I had fun when I did play tennis.
Justine, do you like football?
We used to play football a lot in school.
In Canada, we call it soccer.
We would play soccer all the time at school when I was growing up.
And it's okay.
I don't love soccer.
What about you, James?
Do you like playing football?
Ah, you know.
I love playing football, but I don't play football now.
I used to play football.
I used to play football when I was a child.
But now I don't play football.
But yes, I do like football.
And it is called football.
In the UK, we don't call it soccer.
We call it football.
Okay, that is all for today.
Thank you for being here with me today, James.
And we'll see you in the next video of questions about the things that we like
and the things that we don't like.
Bye.