Hi everyone, I'm Justine and today I'm here with James.
James and I are going to talk about vegetables.
James, do you like carrots?
Hmm.
Yes, Justine. I do like carrots.
Carrots are orange and they are very healthy.
So yes, I do like carrots.
Justine, do you like carrots?
I do like carrots.
Carrots are healthy.
Carrots are good for your body.
And I like the way that carrots taste.
James, do you like cucumbers?
Yes, I do like cucumbers.
Cucumbers are also healthy.
And I like to put cucumbers in a burger.
I like to put cucumbers in a burger.
Justine, what color are cucumbers?
Cucumbers are green.
The peel on the outside of the cucumber is green, dark green,
and the inside of the cucumber is light green.
Cucumbers are green.
Justine, do you like onions?
I like onions when they are cooked.
Cooked onions taste good with other vegetables.
I really like to eat cooked onions with cooked sweet potatoes.
But cooked onions are also really good on burgers.
I like to eat cooked onions on my burgers.
Do you like that, James?
Yes, I love putting cooked onions in my burger.
And it's delicious.
Onions are also very healthy.
So yes, I love onions.
James, it sounds like we both like a lot of vegetables.
But do you have any vegetables that you don't like?
I don't like Brussels sprouts.
Yes, usually you eat Brussels sprouts during Christmas.
But I don't like Brussels sprouts.
Justine, do you have any vegetables that you don't like?
I don't like turnips.
Turnips are another vegetable that are often eaten at Christmas.
And I do not like turnips.
But I do like Brussels sprouts.
So I will eat the Brussels sprouts.
And will you eat the turnip?
Yes, you can eat the Brussels sprouts.
And I will eat the turnips.
Yes.
One more vegetable that I don't like is eggplant.
I don't like the taste of eggplant.
I think in the UK you call eggplants over jeans.
Is that right?
Yes, we don't call them eggplants.
No.
In the UK we call them over jeans.
Okay, so James, do you like over jeans?
Yes, I do like over jeans.
I don't love over jeans.
No.
Okay.
But I like over jeans because over jeans are healthy.
And your jeans are good for your body.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching the video.
And make sure to watch our next video in this series.
Bye.