Hello everybody, my name is Sam and welcome back to English Spanche. Today we are going
to be talking about clothes. We are going to be talking about clothes. Are you ready?
Let's get started.
So these are clothes. All of these are clothes. Here we have one, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen.
Eighteen different types of clothes here. Cool, let's start with number one or a. These are jeans.
These are jeans. Jeans are trousers. These are jeans. These are blue jeans. These are blue jeans.
This is a t-shirt. This is a t-shirt, like this. This is a t-shirt. This is a green t-shirt. This is a green t-shirt.
These are sunglasses. These are sunglasses. We wear sunglasses when it's sunny.
These are sunglasses. These are purple sunglasses. This is a dress. This is a dress.
This is a pink dress. This is a pink dress with purple flowers. This is a pink
dress with purple flowers. This is a jacket. This is a jacket. This is a yellow jacket.
This is a yellow jacket. This is a yellow jacket with fur around the neck and on the
coughs. This is a yellow jacket with fur. This is a tie. This is a tie. We wear ties around our neck to look smart.
This is a tie. This is a green tie with yellow dots. This is a suit. This is a suit. This is a black suit.
This is a black suit. Maybe a little bit grey. This is a black suit. We wear suits to be smart.
This is a rain jacket. This is a rain jacket. This is an orange rain jacket. It keeps us dry. It keeps us dry when it's
raining. This is an orange rain jacket. These are sandals. These are sandals. These are yellow sandals with pink or purple straps.
This is a blouse. This is a blouse. This is a pink blouse. This is a pink blouse. It's very pretty.
This is a scarf. This is a scarf. We wear a scarf around our neck when it's cold. We wear a scarf around our neck when it's cold.
This is a yellow scarf. We might call it leopard print. This is a leopard print scarf. This is a bag.
This is a bag. This bag has red and white stripes. This is a bag with red and white stripes.
And a gold star. This bag also has a gold star. These are trousers. These are trousers. These are yellow trousers.
These are yellow trousers. These are trainers. These are trainers. We wear trainers when doing sports, when doing sports like running or other things.
These are trainers. These are white trainers. These are shorts. These are shorts. These are grain shorts.
This is a hat. This is a hat. This is a hat. This is a red hat with a white brim. This is a red and white hat.
This is a skirt. This is a skirt. This is a purple skirt with pink. This is more pink. This is a purple and pink skirt.
And last but not least, this is a shirt. This is a shirt. This is a shirt. This is a white shirt. This is a white shirt.
These lines are stripes. These lines are stripes. So this is a white stripey shirt. This is a white stripey shirt.
So thank you all for watching this video. I hope you learned some new words today. Leave a like, comment and subscribe to English Spongebob.
I will see you in the next video. Goodbye.