Hello everybody, my name is Sam and welcome back to English Spongebob. Today we are going
to be talking about our faces.
This is hair. This is hair. This is hair. I have brown hair. I have brown hair. I have
long brown hair and I have short brown hair. I have long brown hair and short brown hair.
This is my forehead. This is my forehead. These are my eyebrows. These are my eyebrows. These are my eyes.
I look with my eyes. I look with my eyes. This is my nose. This is my nose. I smell with my nose. I smell.
with my nose. These are my ears. I have big ears. These are my ears. I hair with my ears. I hair with my ears. I hair with my ears.
This is my mouth. I speak with my mouth. I speak with my mouth. These are my teeth. These are my teeth. I bite with my teeth. I bite.
I bite with my teeth. This is a mustache. This is a mustache. And this almost is a beard. This is a beard. I shave my beard.
This is my face.