This is a chili.
Here this is a chili.
And there is a man and the man chops the chili.
He chops it.
He chops the chili.
He is using a knife to chop the chili.
See here this is a knife and the man is using the knife to chop the chili.
He chops the chili in half.
In half.
Now there are two pieces of chili.
Here is one piece of chili and here is another piece of chili.
Because the chili has been chopped in half using a knife.
But chili is very spicy.
Very spicy.
And the man is trying to eat the chili but it is too spicy.
It is too spicy for him.
This is the moon.
It is the moon.
And it is nighttime.
It is not the daytime.
It is nighttime.
And the moon here, the moon is in the sky.
The moon is in the sky at nighttime.
There is a moon and there are also many stars as well.
How many stars can you see?
How many stars?
Let me see.
One star, two stars, three stars, four stars, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven,
twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen and seventeen.
So there are seventeen stars that we can see in the picture.
So there is the moon.
There are seventeen stars in the sky.
And we also see some hills.
There are two hills here.
Here is one hill and here is another hill.
So there are two hills that we can see here.
This is the sun.
And now it is daytime.
It is not nighttime anymore.
It is now daytime.
We can see the sun here.
And we can also see two clouds.
There are two clouds in the sky.
Here is one cloud.
Here is another cloud.
So there are two clouds in the sky.
The sun is coming up right now.
The sun is coming up.
It is sunrise now.
Mm-hmm.
Right now it is sunrise.
The sun is rising.
It is rising because it's sunrise now.
The sun is rising from behind the hills.
Behind the two hills the sun is rising.
Now the sun is not rising.
No.
The sun is not coming up.
The sun is going down.
Now.
This is sunset.
Mm-hmm.
This here.
This is called sunset.
The sun is setting.
The sun is setting right now.
The sun is setting behind the two hills.
You see it's setting just behind this hill here, just here.
Now there are three clouds in the sky.
One cloud, two clouds and now three clouds.
So this is sunrise and this is sunset.
Sunrise and sunset.
This is a pair of shoes.
So these are shoes.
I think orange or red, orange or red shoes.
I will say orange.
These are orange shoes here.
Now this boy, this boy here, he puts on the shoes.
You see?
He puts the shoes on right here.
You see this?
He is putting on the shoes right now.
Also, the boy is wearing socks.
Here is one sock and here is another sock.
See, there are two socks.
The boy is wearing a pair of socks and he is putting on his shoes now.
Now the boy is taking off his shoes.
He is taking the shoes off.
Is he putting on the shoes?
No, he's not putting on the shoes.
He's taking the shoes off, actually.
He's taking them off.
So here he takes off the orange shoes.
This is a book.
Actually, this is a green book.
It's a green book.
Is it a blue book?
No, it's not a blue book.
It's a green book.
This is a shelf.
You see?
This here.
This is a shelf.
How many books are on the shelf?
One book, two books, three books, four, five, six books.
There are six books on the shelf.
There is a blue book and a yellow book.
There are two pink books.
There is a red book and there is a green book.
So there are many different colors of book on the shelf.
The man here, he takes the green book off the shelf.
Here he takes the green book off the shelf.
Here, now, sorry, it is not a man.
It is not a man.
It is a girl.
This is a girl here.
I think it is a young girl.
The girl opens the book.
See?
She opens the book.
And now, the book is open.
This is an open book.
Yeah.
Is the book closed?
No.
The book is not closed.
The book is open.
It's not closed.
Now this girl is reading the book.
She is reading the green book, which is open.
The green book is open and she is reading it.
Now she closes.
She closes the book.
Now.
And now the book is closed.
Is the book open?
No.
The book is not open now.
The book is closed.
So the book is closed.
And now she will put the green book back on the shelf.
So right here, you can see, you can see, she is putting the green book back.
She's putting it back.
She's putting the green book back on the shelf again.
That is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching.
And I will see you in the next one.
Bye-bye.