Hello. Okay, so look at this. Look at this. This is a bird. So this is a bird here.
So then look here. How many birds can you see here? How many birds can you see here?
There are five birds here. Five birds. One, two, three, four, five. So there are five birds here.
Okay, next. Look here. How many birds can you see here? How many birds? There are six birds here.
Six, one, two, three, four, five, six. There are six birds here. Okay. One more, one more. Look here. Look here.
How many birds can you see now? So there are four birds here. Four birds. One, two, three, four. There are four birds here. Okay. Next.
Next. Look here. This, this is a dog. So this is a dog. Right. So look here. How many dogs can you see here? How many dogs can you see?
There are three dogs here. One, two, three. So there are three dogs here. Right. Next. Look here. How many dogs can you see now? How many dogs can you see?
So now there are seven dogs. So there are seven dogs here. Now. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. So there are seven dogs here. Okay. One more. One more. Right. Look here. Look here. How many dogs can you see here?
How many dogs can you see here?
Now there are eight dogs. So there are eight dogs here. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight. So there are eight dogs here. Okay. Right. Next.
Next. Look here. Look here. This, this is a cat. So this is a cat here. Okay. So look here. How many cats can you see here? How many cats are there?
Okay. So there are seven cats here. Seven cats. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. So there are seven cats here. Okay. Next. Look here. How many cats can you see here?
So there are nine. There are now nine cats here. So there's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, and nine. So there are nine cats here now. Okay. One more. One more. One more. Okay. Look here.
How many cats can you see here? How many cats can you see?
So there are now, there are now eight cats here. There are eight cats. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, and eight. So there are eight cats here. Okay. Good job.
Good job. Thank you. Thank you for watching this video. Goodbye.