Hello, I'm Justine. Today I'm going to tell you about a very bad weekend that I had this summer.
But first I need to tell you four things to help give you some context
to understand why the weekend was so bad.
The first thing is that I do not like driving.
For many years I lived about half an hour away from the closest town.
Half an hour by car away from the closest grocery store,
the bank, you know, all the things you need to do to exist in our life.
We lived half an hour away. So I had to drive all of the time.
And once my kids got older, there was also activities to bring them to.
And so driving for me has been an annoying chore,
an annoying job that I've had to do for decades.
I'm 37 years old. I have been driving since before I was allowed to have my driver's license.
Where I lived in Saskatchewan, we were allowed to get our driver's license at 16 years old.
But I grew up on the farm. So I've been driving before I was even allowed to.
So for many years, driving has felt really, really annoying to me.
The second thing you need to know is that my kids are now in a competitive swim club.
So the sport that they're in is swimming and they practice and are pool in our town
with the rest of their team all summer, but they also have swim meets or swim competitions.
So every weekend I drive to a different city around our town to bring my kids to their swim competitions.
So there's more driving.
The third thing is that my husband and I own a porta potty rental business.
This is a porta potty.
A porta potty is a plastic little building that you go to the bathroom in when there's no regular bathroom facilities available.
So we have about a hundred of these porta potty or portable toilets.
And we rent them out to all different types of businesses.
And this past summer, we had all of our porta potty rented out and then there was a forest fire.
There was a forest fire close to our town and there was hundreds of firefighters that came from all over the country and even all over the world.
There was some firefighters that came from Australia and some from the United States.
And so there was hundreds of firefighters that came to help put out the forest fire.
And they needed porta potties.
But it was the weekend.
And the place where we buy the porta potties from is nine and a half hours of driving away.
So the place to buy porta potties was not open and it was the weekend.
So we stole a bunch of our porta potties back from all the different businesses that were renting them.
So we needed about 15 porta potties for the forest fire.
And so we took a bunch of porta potties away from the other businesses.
For example, there was a construction crew that had four porta potties.
So we took two of their porta potties away.
We left them with two porta potties and then we took two back.
And we took one from here and three from there and one from over there.
And then we had enough porta potties to bring to the firefighters.
And we told all of these businesses, hey, sorry, we got an emergency.
Everybody understands we need to keep these firefighters happy with their portable bathrooms.
And we'll give you back your porta potties within a week.
We will make it we will make it right as soon as we can.
We're just in a big crunch.
We are having a big crunch time.
It's a big problem right now.
And we'll get it sorted out.
We just need these.
We need to take them back from you just for a few days.
So that's information number three.
And information number four is that it was actually a long weekend.
So in Canada at the end of July and the beginning of August,
we have a long weekend.
That means that there's an extra day on the end of the weekend.
So Monday was a day off.
So we could not buy porta potties until Tuesday.
Another thing is that my kids had a really important swim competition that weekend.
It was the last swim competition of the year before provincials.
Provincials is when the best athletes from the province,
the whole province all come together and compete at the last competition of the year.
So this competition was the second last competition.
And it was the competition where everybody tries to swim as fast as they can
and make it to provincials.
They want to make it into the top three swimmers
so that they can get to provincials.
So my kids really needed to go to this swim competition.
So that's okay.
We drove to the swim competition on Friday.
And then I drove from the swim competition to the other city on Sunday and Monday.
And then I bought the potties on Tuesday.
And then I drove home.
But this is how it all happened.
So on Friday I drove two hours, two hours to the city where the swim competition was being held.
And then my kids swim on Saturday and Sunday.
And during the swim competitions I'm a volunteer.
So all day long I'm helping run the swim meet.
There's many, many parents that help to run the swim meet.
And it's a lot of fun.
We really enjoy working together and making the swim meet happen.
And watching our kids do really well with their swimming.
But it was 37 or 38 degrees Celsius.
It was so hot.
It was so sunny.
And we were camping.
We had a tent.
And it was really hot.
We ended up being able to sleep in a camper with our friends.
And they had air conditioning.
So that helped it not be quite so difficult.
So we shared a camper with our friends.
And we slept in this other city on Friday night and Saturday night.
Then my kids made it to provincials.
My kids swam so well that they made it to the provincial competition.
And that meant that on Monday they had an extra practice.
All of the swimmers who made it to provincials stayed at the pool to have an extra practice
altogether.
But I needed to go to Calgary.
I needed to go to this other city to buy the porta-potties.
So luckily my friends let my kids stay with them on Sunday night.
And then my kids got a ride back to our house with these other friends.
But on Sunday night I had to start my drive to Calgary.
So I was in a city called Camloops.
And Camloops is about seven hours away from Calgary.
Or seven and a half hours away from Calgary.
So my plan was to drive three or four hours and stay at a city called Revelstock overnight.
And then continue my drive on Monday.
Sleep in Calgary on Monday.
Pick up the potties on Tuesday and then drive home.
But that's not what happened.
On Sunday night I started my drive and I got to Revelstock around 10 pm or 11 maybe.
And I could not find a hotel room.
It was Sunday night on a long weekend and I did not call a head.
There was no, there's not enough time for me to plan ahead my hotel room.
And so most of the hotel rooms in Revelstock had probably been booked four or five months ago.
So Revelstock is a very busy tourist town.
Everybody's enjoying beautiful British Columbia.
Except for me.
I could not find a hotel room.
I went to every hotel I could find.
And I called a bunch more hotels.
Some of them even laughed at me.
When I called to ask if there was a room available for the night, they said,
no, it is Revelstock on a long weekend.
There is no hotel rooms available.
Are you kidding?
No, I'm not kidding actually.
I'm quite desperate.
But thanks anyway.
So there was no place for me to sleep in Revelstock.
I was so tired after helping at the swim meet all weekend and having a long drive
from Cameloups to Revelstock.
I was really desperate.
Plus I had to go pee.
And there was no gas stations open.
You could buy gas, but you could not go inside the gas station to go to the bathroom.
And the restaurants didn't let you in unless you buy something.
And I don't like buying something at McDonald's anyway.
So I didn't want to do that.
So I kept driving.
It was now, it was probably midnight.
And I just kept driving.
I knew that there would be a outhouse on the side of the road.
There's often a place where you can pull out with your car and park for a little while.
And there's often an outhouse.
It's just a little toilet with a hole in the ground.
And everybody goes to the bathroom in the outhouse.
And so that's what I did.
I drove probably for 20 more minutes.
And I found one of those outhouses so that I could go pee.
And then I decided to park my truck there and sleep for a little while.
Because it was not safe for me to keep driving.
Because I was so tired.
And angry.
So I slept in my truck for two or three hours.
But I didn't really sleep.
I was kind of cold.
I was uncomfortable.
I didn't have any blankets or pillows because I wasn't planning on sleeping in my truck.
And so I woke up around three in the morning and I kept driving.
The next city is called Golden.
And it was about three hours away from Rebelsdok.
And there was no hotel rooms available there either.
There was no chance of me getting a hotel room.
Everything had been booked months ahead of time.
And another problem I have is because I was driving a truck with a long trailer.
So I couldn't just drive into every hotel and ask them.
Because there was no room in the parking lots.
So I found one hotel that had a big parking lot that I could sit in.
And so I went to that hotel and I told the guy, I know you do not have any hotel rooms available.
But I'm wondering if there's one place that I could sleep for like five hours.
Please.
I told him my whole story and I told him how desperate I was and I need to get to Calgary.
And I just cannot keep driving.
I need to sleep.
And so he said yes, we have one where we have a person checking in at about three o'clock.
So that means that you need to leave at noon so that my cleaners can get in and clean the bed
before the next people come.
And it was six in the morning.
So I said six in the morning until noon.
Perfect.
I love that.
I'm in.
But guess how much it cost.
Just guess.
Take a wild guess.
How much do you think this hotel room cost for six hours?
$481.
And I paid it because I was so, so desperate.
I paid $481 to sleep in a hotel room for six hours.
Crazy.
Absolutely crazy.
Have I lost my mind?
Yes.
I think I did lose my mind a little bit.
But I got it back because I had a good sleep.
I had such a good sleep.
I had a hot shower.
I climbed into bed and I had the best sleep for like four or five hours.
And then I got up and kept driving.
I drove the last few hours to Calgary.
And I checked into my hotel there.
So now it was Monday afternoon, maybe like four or five o'clock in the afternoon.
And I slept again.
And then I got up on Tuesday.
I went to the place to buy my porta-potties.
And then I drove home.
I drove all the way home in one trip from Calgary back to my town.
And it was about nine and a half hours of actual driving.
But I stopped a lot to rest and stretch and eat some good food.
I don't like eating like drive through like fast food.
So I like to stop and get something from the grocery store or get something a little bit more
enjoyable than just fast food stuff.
So I like to take my time when I can.
So in total it was about a 12 or a 13 hour trip with all of my stops.
And it's a really beautiful drive.
I have to admit that between Calgary, Alberta and driving through the mountains in British Columbia,
it is a beautiful landscape.
There's amazing mountains with beautiful trees and there's waterfalls and there's rivers.
And there's a lot of beautiful things that you can do along the way.
But I was so annoyed that I was just driving.
I was listening to my podcast and I just drove and I was like get me out of here.
I hate every minute of this.
I just want to be home and I do not want to ever do this again.
But I did stop to take this picture.
It's a pretty beautiful picture.
It has my truck and my trailer with all of my bright green porta-potties on it.
And it shows the mountains in the background.
This picture was taken at Rogers Pass, which is one of the mountains on the highway
that I was driving on.
And I know it's a pretty beautiful place, but I was not in a mental state to be able to enjoy it.
I was just so mad.
But all in all, it worked out really well.
We were able to get these porta-potties and give them back to all of the people
that we stole porta-potties from.
The firefighters appreciated the porta-potties that we gave them.
And they controlled the forest fire and nobody got hurt and nobody's properties were damaged.
And it all worked out.
And I was a hero because I drove 10 hours to Caliari and 10 hours back.
And endured torture on the way.
But I made it.
So that is the story of my very bad weekend that I had in the summer.
Thanks for watching. Bye.