Hello. Okay. This is an apple. This is an apple here. Now, how many apples are there?
How many apples are there? There are two apples here. One, two, two apples here. Okay. Next, now, how many apples are there?
There are three apples now. One, two, three. Three apples here. Okay. Next, now, how many apples are there?
There are now five apples here. One, two, three, four, five. There are five apples here. Okay. Next. This, this is an orange. This is an orange.
So, how many oranges are there? There are three oranges here. Okay. Next, now, how many oranges are there?
There are now five oranges. Five oranges here. Next. Okay. How many oranges are there now?
There are now four. There's four oranges here. Okay. Next. Look at this. Look at this. This is a banana. This is a banana here. Okay. So, how many bananas can you see here?
How many bananas can you see? There are four bananas here. Four bananas. Okay. Next. Look here. How many bananas are there here?
Now, there are six bananas here. So, there are six bananas here now. Six. Okay. One more. One more. Look here. How many bananas can you see here? How many?
Yes. There are five bananas here now. Okay. Next. Next. Take a look. Look here and see how many bananas, how many apples and how many oranges are there here? How many can you see here?
Okay. So, there are six apples here. There are three oranges and there are four bananas here. Thank you. Thank you for watching this video. Thank you. Bye-bye.