Hello, so I am going to talk, talk about what I can do and what I can't do.
So I can swim.
I can swim.
Also, I can drive.
I can drive also.
Yes.
And also, I can speak Spanish.
I can speak Spanish.
Well I'm a ghost.
Catal.
I can speak Spanish.
But.
I can't.
I can't speak French.
No, no, no, no.
Also.
Also, I can't speak German.
No, I can't speak German.
But I can speak Spanish.
And you.
Can you speak Spanish?
Can you drive?
Can you swim?
Can you speak English?
I can't fly a plane.
No, no, no, no.
I can't do that.
I can't fly a plane.
Also, also, I can't do a backflip.
No, I can't.
I can't do a backflip.
Can you?
Can you fly a plane?
Can you do a backflip?
This is David.
Now, David can swim.
David can swim.
But.
But David can't.
He can't drive.
No, David can't drive.
Now David can speak French.
Mm-hmm.
David can speak French.
But.
But David can't.
He can't speak German.
No, David can't speak German.
Also.
Also, David can't do a backflip.
And David can't fly a plane either.
This is Emma.
This is Emma now.
Emma can drive.
And Emma can swim.
And also, also Emma can speak English.
She can speak English.
So she can drive.
She can swim.
And she can speak English.
But.
She can't speak French.
She can't speak German.
Also.
She can't do a backflip.
And.
She can't fly a plane.
So you.
Can you speak English?
Can you speak French?
Can you speak German?
Can you drive?
Can you swim?
Can you do a backflip?
Can you fly a plane?
Thank you for watching this video.
Bye bye.