Hi Brian.
Hi.
How are you?
I'm great.
And you?
How are you?
I'm good, thanks.
Brian, where are you from?
I'm from New York City.
And you?
Where are you from?
I'm from Oxford in the UK.
How old are you?
I am 45 years old.
And you?
How old are you?
I am 32 years old.
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
I do.
I have one younger brother.
And you?
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Yeah, I have one brother and two sisters.
So, what's your favourite food?
My favourite food is steak.
And you?
What's your favourite food?
My favourite food is pizza.
And what's your favourite sport?
I have two favourite sports.
I love baseball and I love soccer.
And you?
What's your favourite sport?
My favourite sport is tennis.
Brian, can you swim?
I can swim very well.
And you?
Can you swim?
Yeah, I can swim.
Can you ride a bicycle?
I can ride a bicycle.
And you?
Can you ride a bike?
Yeah, I can ride a bike.
And can you drive?
I can drive.
Yes.
And you?
Can you drive?
Yeah, I can drive.
Brian, thank you for talking with me today.
Thank you, James.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
American, British, Australian and also other accents.
You can choose which topic you want to listen to.
And you can choose which grammar point you want to focus on.
The website will track your time.
So you can see how many minutes you have listened to Comprehensible Input.
Today, yesterday and for the whole month.
So go to Englishspongeb.com.
The link is in the description of the video.